(Amy:)While I was charming, supportive,
and let's face it...
(Amy:)...in this dress, the perfect combination
of Madonna and whore.
- Oh, God, did he make a move on you?
- No, but it's only a matter of time.
(Amy:)How could I have not seen this coming?
(Amy:)Now I'm gonna have to break
the little sad sack's heart.
(Penny:)I'm sure he'll be okay.
(Amy:)Oh, Penny.
Much as I would treasure knowing...
(Amy:)...the two of us had been defiled
by the same man...
(Amy:)...Leonard just doesn't get
my motor running.
(Penny:)So, um, what are you gonna do?
Do you want me to talk to Leonard?
(Penny:)- Let him down easy.
- No. I'll let him have tonight.
(Amy:)I'll send him an e-mail...
(Amy:)...letting him know this body
is never gonna be his wonderland.
(Amy:)I mean, frankly, you've got a better shot
than he does.